http://www.cspotwin.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home »
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Brooke Scudder’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, http://www.brookescudder.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
Recent Posts
What You Need to Know about Judo and Kickboxing
Tree Care Tips During Winter
Questions to Ask Before You Hire an Electrician
Why Should Millennials Invest In Buying a Property?
Faulty Mistakes We Don’t Mind About Controlling the Weeds
Search for:
Recent Comments
CS Pot WinWhat You Need to Know about Judo and Kickboxing November 25, 2020There are so many different ways wherein you could practice martial arts. There are so many martial arts today and almost all of them are taught all around the globe because more and more people are getting very much interested with the benefits that martial arts could give to people. If you are going to […] secure_adminTree Care Tips During Winter  October 2, 2020Winter is here now. However, that is not an excuse to skip taking care of your trees. In fact, winter is the best time to maintain and take care of your trees. It is the ideal time to guarantee that your trees are in great condition as well, which leads to warmer seasons. Here is […] secure_adminQuestions to Ask Before You Hire an Electrician  August 12, 2020Regardless if it’s your first time hiring an electrician in your life, or you want to look for a new electrician to work with, it’s essential to look for someone with the proper experience and expertise. The following questions will aid you to find for the best Limerick City electrician to work with:  Do you clean […] secure_adminWhy Should Millennials Invest In Buying a Property? April 27, 2020Nowadays, young people tend to move more often and the instability of the job could be an issue in several industries. With several millennials now who prioritize experiences over assets, owning a condo or a home might be the last thing listed on their priority list. But, investing in even a small property within a […] secure_adminFaulty Mistakes We Don’t Mind About Controlling the Weeds April 24, 2020For those experts, they would see things properly and correctly and make sure that there won’t be any problems when it comes to their expertise especially for those people who are working under the lawn care maintenance and services. As they will they will give their very best and excellent output to ensure that there […] secure_admin Archives
November 2020
October 2020
August 2020
April 2020
Categories
Electrical Service
Lawn Services
Leasing Services
